automobile insurance some level of
automobile insurance is required by law
in most places even if you are not
required to have it and you are driving
an old clunker that has been paid off
for years automobile insurance is
something you should not skip if you are
involved in an accident and someone is
injured or their property is damaged you
may be subject to a lawsuit that could
cost you everything you own accident
happen quickly and the results are often
tragic having no automobile insurance or
purchasing only the minimum required
coverage saves you only a teeny amount
of money and puts everything else you
own at risk
important points this season in addition
to police is listed above business
owners and Business Insurance liability
coverage in a
litigation happy Society could be the
difference between a long prosperous and
aware and a trip to the bankruptcy court
show for insurance carefully insurance
policies come in a variety of shapes and
size and post many different features
benefits and prices show up carefully
read the policies and talk to a licensed
Insurance professional to be certain you
understand the coverage and the cost
make sure the police is you purchase are
advocate for your needs and don't sign
on the dotted line until you are happy
with the purchases
consider enlisting the services of an
insurance broker as they can search for
policies across several insurance
companies to find coverage their best
suits your needs ask the broader
broker to provide you with several
options so you can compare feature
Province and rates be in control of your
protection by being well informed to
make a decision
what is a whole life insurance policy
answer is this a whole life insurance
policy is a permanent life insurance
policy in which death benefits are paid
upon the death of an insured the whole
of policy remains in force for the life
of the insured as long as premiums are
set up to date in addition to death
benefits Whole Life policies build cash
value which can be accessed during the
in short lifetime
question is what is a universal life
insurance policy a universal life UL
insurance policy is permanent life
insurance that allows the policyholder
to invest their cash value in the
separate account which feature funds
tied to the stock market it is a
flexible policy where by premiums and
head that benefits can be adjusted
how do you cancel an insurance policy a
policyholder must cancel an insurance
policy according to the cancellation
provision for their contract often
insurers allow policyholders to cancel
by phone however some requires the
request in writing what is an umbrella
insurance policy and afraid of policy is
liability insurance that provides
additional coverage in excess of the
policy holder current policy limits for
example it damages exceed the limits of
a policy holder property insurance for
example Home Auto the umbrella policy
will provide the additional liability
coverage up to the policy limits this
type of insurance most benefit those
with sizeable access which could be
adjusted to Caesar for more videos
please like And subscribe my channel
thank you